<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title> on Exercism Command-Line Client </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://cli.exercism.io/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://cli.exercism.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cli.exercism.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Chat Find our support channel on Gitter.
GitHub Issues Open an issue in exercism/cli.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Exercism</title>
      <link>http://cli.exercism.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cli.exercism.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Exercism is an open source project that aims to give people a way to get from that awkward &amp;ldquo;Hello, World!&amp;rdquo; in a new programming language to being fluent and at ease with the basic constructs, idioms and standard library of the language.
The project supports over 40 programming languages, each of which contains numerous small exercises. You work on the exercises locally, in your own development environment and favorite text editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Usage</title>
      <link>http://cli.exercism.io/usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cli.exercism.io/usage/</guid>
      <description>Run the help subcommand to get the full list of available commands.
exercism help  Configuration You need to tell the tool who you are:
exercism configure --key=YOUR\_API\_KEY  Visit exercism.io/account/key to get your api key.
You can override other configuration options. Run exercism configure without any arguments to see the available options.
Downloading exercises You download exercises for a track with the fetch command. Replace $TRACK_ID with the ID of the track you are working on, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shell completion scripts</title>
      <link>http://cli.exercism.io/scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cli.exercism.io/scripts/</guid>
      <description>Bash Install the CLI bash-completion script by downloading it and sourcing it in your shell config.
mkdir -p ~/.config/exercism curl http://cli.exercism.io/shell/exercism\_completion.bash &amp;gt; ~/.config/exercism/exercism\_completion.bash  Load the completion in your .bashrc, .bash_profile or .profile by adding the following snippet:
if [ -f ~/.config/exercism/exercism_completion.bash ]; then source ~/.config/exercism/exercism_completion.bash fi  Zsh Install the CLI bash-completion script by downloading it and sourcing it in your shell config.
mkdir -p ~/.config/exercism curl http://cli.exercism.io/shell/exercism\_completion.zsh &amp;gt; ~/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>http://cli.exercism.io/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cli.exercism.io/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>Make sure you are on the latest version.
Verify which version you are on:
exercism -v  Verify against the latest release and upgrade if your version is not the most recent.
After upgrading, double-check the version. If the version didn&amp;rsquo;t change, make sure you are running the upgraded binary.
which exercism  If you are still having trouble open an issue in exercism/cli on GitHub with the output of the debug command.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

